Angela Robinette

Front End Developer

Email: <u>angela@dev-angela.com</u> Website: <u>www.dev-angela.com</u> Phone: 406-671-1693

* HTML * CSS * JavaScript * Accessibility * Security

Profile:

My coding journey began as a hobby in 2000. First, I worked with HTML and was hooked. A few years later, I learned CSS. Finally, I taught myself a bit of JavaScript for a hidden picture game.

I graduated from Purdue University Global - Summa Cum Laude - with an Associate degree in Software Development/Computer Programming. I love creating beautiful, functional web pages that enhance a user's experience and are secure and accessible to all. During my internship at PGIP-Tech, I was the software development lead. I went back afterward and became a mentor.

Education:

Purdue University Global

4.0 GPA Associate Degree Graduation – March 15, 2022

Montana State University Bozeman, MT

1994-1995 General Studies

Montana State University

Billings, MT

1996-1997 English Major

Colstrip High School

High School Diploma, Class of 1994

Experience:

PGIP-Tech Internship January 2022 – Present

SofDev Mentor

Dev-angela.com

January 2022 – Present Owner/Designer/Developer **PGIP-Tech Internship** 10/14/2021 – 12/21/2021 SofDev Manager

Skills:

HTML 15+ years experience CSS 15+ years experience Paintshop Pro 15+ years experience JavaScript 10+ years experience

Git 2+ years experience Bootstrap 1+ years experience

Experience using:

PHP Docker SQL C# Angular